The Park Is Mine is a tv movie, action, drama film
directed by Steven Hilliard Stern.
A Vietnam vet takes forceful control of Central Park to remember
those who served and died in the Vietnam War.
Mitch, played by Tommy Lee Jones.
Valery, played by Helen Shaver.
Eubanks, played by Yaphet Kotto.
Commissioner Keller, played by Lawrence Dane.
Dix, played by Peter Dvorsky.
Mike, played by Eric Peterson.
The Park Is Mine is a Canadian-American drama television film based
on the novel of the same name by Stephen Peters.
The film explores themes of vietnam veteran, new york city,
suicide, based on novel or book, police.
The tone is emotional.